[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What is the capital of United states of America?",
    "options": ["Washington D.C.", "New York", "Chicago", "Los Angeles"],
    "Answer": "Washington D.C.",
    "status": "U"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Who was the first person to go to moon?",
    "options": ["Gagarin", "Einstein", "Shakespear", "Armstrong"],
    "Answer": "Armstrong",
    "status": "U"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Which compound has a chemical formula as 'H2O'?",
    "options": ["Oxygen", "Water", "Carbon", "Acid"],
    "Answer": "Water",
    "status": "U"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Who won the Soccer World Cup in 2018?",
    "options": ["Brazil", "Italy", "Germany", "France"],
    "Answer": "France",
    "status": "U"
  },
 {
  "id": 5,
  "question": "How many Kilometers are there in 100 miles?",
  "options": ["1256", "161", "25", "100"],
  "Answer": "161",
  "status": "U"
},
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Which time zone does Los Angeles lie in?",
    "options": ["CST", "PST", "MST", "DST"],
    "Answer": "PST",
    "status": "U"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "On Which Day do we celebrate independence day in USA?",
    "options": ["June 2", "December 25", "May 12", "July 4"],
    "Answer": "July 4",
    "status": "U"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Which blood group is called as the universal donor?",
    "options": ["A", "B", "O", "AB"],
    "Answer": "O",
    "status": "U"
  }, {
  "id": 9,
  "question": "What is the full form of W.W.W. in computer terminology?",
  "options": ["Wonderful World Web", "World Wide Wrapped", "World Wide Web", "Wiki Web World"],
  "Answer": "World Wide Web",
  "status": "U"
},
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Which is the largest Planet of Solar System?",
    "options": ["Jupiter", "Mars", "Saturn", "Neptune"],
    "Answer": "Jupiter",
    "status": "U"
  }
]
